freeclassifiedsworld.com 2016-11-08

# Andhra Pradesh, India - Post Free Ads Without Registration - Free Classifieds World

## Privacy Policy

Post Free Ads Without Registration - Free Classifieds World has established this privacy policy to explain to you how your information is protected, collected and used, which may be updated by Post Free Ads Without Registration - Free Classifieds World from time to time. Post Free Ads Without Registration - Free Classifieds World will provide notice of materially significant changes to this privacy policy by posting notice on our site. 

### 1\. Protecting your privacy

  * We run banner ads, pop ups, pop unders, or any other kind of commercial ads.
  * We share your information with third parties for marketing purposes.
  * We engage in cross-marketing or link-referral programs with other sites.
  * We employ tracking devices for marketing purposes ("cookies", "web beacons," single-pixel gifs).
  * We send you unsolicited communications for marketing purposes. 
  * Forums uses basic webserver authentication. Close your browser to log out.
  * Post Free Ads Without Registration - Free Classifieds World knowingly collect any information from persons under the age of 13. If we learns that a posting is by a person under the age of 13, Post Free Ads Without Registration - Free Classifieds World will keep that post.
  * Post Free Ads Without Registration - Free Classifieds World, or people who post on this website, may provide links to third party websites, which may have different privacy practices. We are not responsible for, nor have any control over, the privacy policies of those third party websites, and encourage all users to read the privacy policies of each and every website visited. 

### 2\. Data we collect

  * We sometimes collect your email address, for purposes such as sending self-publishing and confirmation emails, registering for forums, etc.
  * For paid postings, we collect contact information, such as name(s), phone/fax number(s), and address for billing purposes.
  * Post Free Ads Without Registration - Free Classifieds World does not store credit card information. Credit card transactions are transmitted to a financial gateway, and we endeavor to protect the security of your payment information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology.
  * We may collect personal information if you provide it in feedback or comments, post it on our classifieds or interactive forums, or if you contact us directly. Please do not post any personal information on our discussion forums or classifieds posts that you expect to keep private.
  * Our web logs collect standard web log entries for each page served, including your IP address, page URL, and timestamp. Web logs help us to diagnose problems with our server, to administer our website, and to otherwise provide our service to you.

### 3\. Data we store

  * All classified and forum postings are stored in our database, even after "deletion," and may be archived elsewhere.
  * Our web logs and other records are stored indefinitely.
  * Although we make good faith efforts to store the information in a secure operating environment that is not available to the public, we cannot guarantee complete security.

### 4\. Archiving and display of Post Free Ads Without Registration - Free Classifieds World postings by search engines and other sites

Search engines and other sites not affiliated with Post Free Ads Without Registration - Free Classifieds World - including archive.org, google.com, and groups.yahoo.com - archive or otherwise make available Post Free Ads Without Registration - Free Classifieds World ad postings, including resumes. 

### 5\. Circumstances in which Post Free Ads Without Registration - Free Classifieds World may release information

  * We disclose information about the users if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process.
  * Post Free Ads Without Registration - Free Classifieds World also disclose information about its users to law enforcement officers or others, in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to: enforce our Terms of Use; respond to claims that any posting or other content violates the rights of third-parties; or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of craigslist, its users or the general public.

### 6\. Feedback and comments

We welcome your feedback on this document in our [contact form](http://www.freeclassifiedsworld.com/index.php?view=page&pagename=contact). We would be glad to explain you any terms for your better understanding.
